mapleme.com 2015-12-06

# Privacy Policy - Mapleme.com

**MapleMe.com PRIVACY POLICY:**

We honor your privacy and security. Thus, we make in various efforts to maintain and protect your confidentiality. We urge all our users to go through the following points in order to understand our privacy policy in a better and broader manner. 

**PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION of USER**

When you submit a request or electronically pass information to MapleMe.com (including, but not limited to, comments, feedback, employment applications and resumes), you are sometimes asked to provide certain information, including, but not limited to, your name, title, company, address, phone and fax numbers, e-mail address and the line of business. We ask for this personally identifiable information in order to facilitate your requests, provide personalized service and communicate separately with you. Except as otherwise set forth herein, we do not sell, trade, or rent your personally identifiable information to/with any third parties.   
Since we rely on the commercial software and programs of the third parties to operate our servers, we may inadvertently collect personal information due to certain automatic functions or features contained in such software or due to certain software changes or upgrades. We practice reasonable tools to eradicate any such information from our system. Hence, we request our users to notify us promptly of any such unintended collections, to help us take the necessary action to delete such information as soon as possible. 

**CLICKSTREAM DATA**

As you browse through the Internet, a trail of electronic information is left at each website you visit. This information, which is sometimes called "clickstream data", can be collected and stored by a website's server. The clickstream data can not only tell us about the type of computer and browsing software you use, but can also reveal the address of the website from which you linked. Moreover, in some instances, this data can also store your e-mail address. We may use clickstream data to determine how much time the visitors spend on each page of the website and how they navigate through it. However, we will only use this information to improve the website and not for any other purpose. Any collection or use of clickstream data will be anonymous and aggregate, and will not contain any personally identifiable information of the users and the visitors of MapleMe.com. 

**CONSENT TO PROCESSING**

When you provide any information to our website, you must fully understand and unambiguously consent to the collection and processing of such information.

**LEGAL DISCLOSURE; CIRCUMSTANCES OF DISCLOSURE**

Notwithstanding anything to the contrary herein, MapleMe.com shall, pursuant to valid legal process, such as a search warrant, subpoena, or court order, allow access to information, including personally identifiable information, provided to the MapleMe.com or the website in order to comply with such process and to protect our rights and property. If warranted, we may also allow access to this information in special emergencies where physical safety is at risk. MapleMe.com reserves the right to disclose any information obtained from or about you, including but not limited to personally identifiable information, data obtained from internet protocol addresses and clickstream data, to third parties in connection with a merger, acquisition, bankruptcy or sale of all or substantially all of the MapleMe.com assets.

**USER'S ACCEPTANCE OF THIS POLICY**

By visiting the MapleMe.com, you signify your assent to the terms and conditions, mentioned in the privacy policy of the website. If you do not agree with the terms of this privacy policy, please do not use the website. We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions from this privacy policy at any time, with or without a prior notice. Your continued use of the website, following the posting of changes to these terms means you accept these changes.   
If you have any questions or comments regarding the privacy issues of the MapleMe.com, please drop a line to the following mailbox: contact@MapleMe.com. 

**BREACH of SECURITY**

Mapleme.com makes every possible effort to avoid the breach of security. Anyhow, Internet is an open communication medium, so we cannot guarantee or assure that your communication with us will be fully free of any unauthorized interference or access of a Third Party. Thus, you must use the Site at your own risk. 

IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH TERM AND CONDITION MENTIONED HERE THEN PLEASE LEAVE THE WEBSITE IMMEDIATELY. BY USING THIS WEBSITE HENCEFORTH, YOU AUTOMATICALLY AGREE TO ACCEPT AND ABIDE BY ALL TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF MapleMe.com.
